var quiz = [
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 1?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 2
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 2?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 3?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 0
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 4?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 5?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 6?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 2
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 7?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 8?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 0
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 9?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': "Blabedee Blah 10?",
    'options': ['o1', 'o2', 'o3', 'o4'],
    'answer': 1
  },

]
